macysjobs.com 2012-07-21

# Macy's Jobs - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the corporate recruitment web site for Macy's, Inc., and its [subsidiaries](http://www.macysjobs.com/corporate/otherinfo/subsidiaries.asp). This web site ([www.macysjobs.com](http://www.macysjobs.com/)) is owned by Macy's, Inc. and provides you with information on employment opportunities with our company, along with other related information. The street address for Macy's, Inc. is 7 West Seventh Street, Cincinnati, Ohio 45202.

As a premier department store, catalog and Internet retailer, we understand that privacy is important, and we have posted this privacy policy to let you know what types of personal information we collect on this site, how we use it and whether it is shared with any unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis to stay up-to-date on our most current privacy practices, which may change from time to time as we continue to develop this site. The date that this policy last was changed is noted below. 

Please note that this privacy policy applies only to this web site. For the privacy policy of Macy's, Inc.'s corporate web site, which includes press releases and investment news, please refer to Macy's, Inc.'s corporate web site at [www.macysinc.com](http://www.macysinc.com/). For the privacy policies of each of our subsidiaries that operate e-commerce web sites, such as [macys.com](http://macys.com/), or that offer online bill payment options or allow you to apply for a credit card, please refer to those specific web sites.

 **Information Collected When You Visit Our Web site and How We Use It**

Macy's, Inc. only collects personal information that you voluntarily submit to this site, and we use that information for the purpose for which it was submitted. The following are examples of the types of personal information that are collected and how they are used:

  * If you submit a resume for a job posted on our site, that resume will be forwarded to the appropriate subsidiary for review and response. "Applicant Profiles" may be submitted through the "Search Jobs/Apply Now!" online employment center forms available on the [www.macysjobs.com](http://www.macysjobs.com/) web site. However, please do not include sensitive data, such as a social security number, driver's license number, or government issued identification number or account number, when submitting an online application, resume or cover letter. Applicant profiles are kept in our database for future reference so we can continue to consider you for additional positions. All of Macy's, Inc.'s subsidiaries share equally in the access of our database and you may be contacted by a division other than the one to which you originally submitted an applicant profile, or for a position other than one for which you originally submitted an applicant profile. To be removed from the Macy's, Inc. database so future e-mail correspondence regarding employment opportunities will not be sent to you, e-mail your name (first and last), along with your e-mail address to the following link: [macysjobs@macys.com](mailto:macysjobs@macys.com). Please specify in your e-mail that you are requesting to be removed from the Macy's, Inc. database. Note: Submitted applicant profiles are considered by Macy's, Inc. to be a submission of position interest and not a legal application.
  * If you submit a comment about us or one of our subsidiaries through our "Got Questions" form on the college section of the web site, we will use your information to review and respond to your comment or question. In doing so, we may forward the information you provide to one of our subsidiaries. For example, if you submit a comment about Bloomingdale's, we may provide that information to Bloomingdale's so that they may review and, as appropriate, respond to it.
  * If you ask to be added to the mailing list for any of our subsidiaries (e.g., you want to receive macys.com catalogs), we will provide your information to that subsidiary, and you will be added to its marketing list. In that case, please note that your information may be shared with other Macy's, Inc. affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes.

With the exception noted above, we do not use the information you submit to this site for marketing purposes, and we do not share it with any unaffiliated third parties. If you have any questions about our privacy practices and the choices you have regarding the use of your personal information for marketing purposes, you may call our Customer Service Privacy Hotline at 888-529-2254. You also may write to the following address: Macy's Credit and Customer Services Customer Service, ATTN: Privacy Master, P.O. Box 8215, Mason, Ohio 40540.

 **How We Use Cookies**

  * Macy's, Inc. automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information and the page you browsed. However, that information is not used to identify and track you as an individual when you're browsing our site.
  * Macy's, Inc. uses cookies only to customize the look of the site and to offer assistance when completing our forms so that a user is not required to retype the same information. For example, if you have the Macromedia Flash plug-in, we will offer pages that contain Flash animations. Macy's, Inc. does not use cookies to track your movement through the site.

 **Security**

Macy's, Inc. is committed to doing its best to maintain the security of information collected on our site. To try to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, please do not include sensitive data, such as a social security number, driver's license number, or government issued identification number or account number, when submitting an online application, resume or cover letter.

 **Children's Privacy**

Macy's, Inc. does not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age on this web site. It is Macy's, Inc.'s policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act on each of its web sites, as applicable.

This policy was updated last on December 27, 2004.
